Guide to the The University of Montana Department of Native American Studies Records 1921-2003
Maureen and Mike Mansfield Library, The University of Montana--Missoula
- Subject Files, 1921-2003; Series I; 11.5 linear feet
  - Education, Subseries 4
    - Guide to OE-Administered Programs, 1977 (Box-folder 4/21)
    - American Education-Indian Power, 1974 (Box-folder 4/23)
    - Northern Cheyenne Bilingual Education Program, Dan Alford, 1973 (Box-folder 4/25)
    - Guidelines for Teaching Concepts of Fairness, Justice, and Democracy in BIA and Tribal Contract Schools, 1975 (Box-folder 4/26)
    - The Beauty Way & Missionary Way Paper #3, An Educational Comparison, 1978 (Box-folder 4/27)
    - Application for local Education Grants Under the Emergency School Aid Act, 1976 (Box-folder 4/28)
    - Bilingual Education, Eighth Annual Education Seattle, 1979 (Box-folder 4/30)
    - Cherokee Project- Program for children with learning disabilities, 1972 (Box-folder 5/1)
    - Curricula Materials, Education, Simulations Games, undated (Box-folder 5/2)
    - Eight Problems In Indian Education by Alonzo Spang, 1974 (Box-folder 5/4)
    - Department H.E.W. [Health, Education and Welfare] letter, 1977 (Box-folder 5/5)
    - H.E.W. News, 1977 (Box-folder 5/15)
    - A Holistic Educational Philosophy, 1978 (Box-folder 5/16)
    - Suggested Model for Cross-Cultural Goals Change (a), undated (Box-folder 5/17)
    - Indian Education Bureau Of Indian Affairs, Concerted Effort Needed to Improve Indian Education, 1977 (Box-folder 5/20)
    - "Indian educators as a catalyst for Political Reform" by Robert Burnette, 1972 (Box-folder 5/22)
    - Indian Education A special report National Advisory Council on Vocational Education, 1973 (Box-folder 5/23)
    - Indian & Northern Education Program, University of Saskatchewan, undated (Box-folder 5/24)
    - Instruction For Completing Application, Department HEW Indian Education, 1975 (Box-folder 5/28)
    - In-service teacher Education concepts Project, Report 1 "Issues to Face", 1976 (Box-folder 5/29)
    - National Center for Career Education, 1976 (Box-folder 5/30)
    - The National Study of American Indian Education, 1970 (Box-folder 5/32)
    - The National Study of American Indian Education, 1970 (Box-folder 5/33)
    - The Law, Indians, and Education, 1972 (Box-folder 5/34)
    - Office of Indian Education, Education Convocation on Indian Education, 1977 (Box-folder 5/35)
    - Office of Education Report, Daily News Digest, Education Conflicts, 1975 (Box-folder 5/36)
    - The Responsive Educational Program, Far West Laboratory for Education Research and Development, 1973 (Box-folder 5/37)
    - Office of Education Program Service, 1976 (Box-folder 5/38)
    - Language in American Indian Education, 1971 (Box-folder 7/3)
    - Assessing Teaching Styles in Indian Education, 1980-1988 and undated (Box-folder 7/5)
    - Cooperative Learning and the Native American Student, 1989, 1991 and undated (Box-folder 7/6)
    - Kamensky, Mary, Cultural Diversity Workshops, 1991-1997 and undated (Box-folder 7/7)
    - Montana High School Enrollment, 1990-1993 (Box-folder 7/8)
    - "The Role of a Tribal College" by Hans P. Zaglauer, 1991 (Box-folder 8/3)
    - Problems In Indian Education Exercise, undated (Box-folder 8/4)
    - Possible Projects or Research Topics About Indians, undated (Box-folder 8/5)
    - Questions to Consider in Seminars, undated (Box-folder 8/6)
    - Reading List, Indians & Education, undated (Box-folder 8/7)
    - A mother to a teacher, Respect My Child: He has a right to be himself, undated (Box-folder 8/8)
    - So you want to Improve Your School? Here's some ideas from Colville's Project!, undated (Box-folder 8/9)
    - Is this what schools are for ? by Kathryn Johnston Noyes & Gordon L. McAndrew, undated (Box-folder 8/10)
    - The Indian Awareness Inventory Directions and Resources for usage, undated (Box-folder 8/11)
    - Indian Education, Department of Indian Affairs and Northern Development, 1967 (Box-folder 8/12)
    - Montana Teacher Aid Comparison Survey Results, 1972 (Box-folder 8/13)
    - Multicultural Materials, 1978 (Box-folder 8/14)
    - Suggested projects or Research topics on Indians, undated (Box-folder 8/16)
    - Home Economics Education, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 8/19)
    - Ideas RE: Science Interest & Motivation, Education Briefing Paper, undated (Box-folder 8/20)
    - Education Briefing Paper, Cooperative Education, 1975 (Box-folder 8/21)
    - Education Briefing Paper, Bilingual Education, 1975 (Box-folder 8/22)
    - Educators of Native Americans, 1976 (Box-folder 8/23)
    - Evaluation, Integration and Selection of Indian Studies Material by McClusky, undated (Box-folder 8/24)
    - Examples of Institutional Racism in Education, undated (Box-folder 8/25)
    - Examples of Key Concerns, undated (Box-folder 8/26)
    - The Executive Director Speaks Out, Coalition of Indian-Controlled School Boards, undated (Box-folder 8/27)
    - General Criteria for Evaluating Textbooks, 1976 (Box-folder 8/28)
    - To Help, Not To Homogenize Native American Children, 1974 (Box-folder 8/29)
    - In Defense of Open Admission, 1970 (Box-folder 8/30)
    - Indian College Enrollment, 1972 and undated (Box-folder 8/31)
    - Indian Schools, Regimented Non-Education, 1969 (Box-folder 8/33)
    - Indian Parent Involvement in Education, 1972 (Box-folder 8/34)
    - The Indian Student is NOT Low Man on The Totem Pole by Madison Coombs, 1970 (Box-folder 8/36)
    - Integrity Before Education, undated (Box-folder 8/38)
    - Possible Determinants of Career Patterns, undated (Box-folder 8/39)
    - Relevant Speech Education For the American Indian, 1970 and undated (Box-folder 8/40)
    - BIA Higher Education Grant Program, 1976 (Box-folder 9/1)
    - American Indian Unit, primary grade, undated (Box-folder 9/2)
    - American Indian Exceptional Children Background paper, 1976 (Box-folder 9/3)
    - Bilingual Education, Who Benefits, 1973 and undated (Box-folder 9/4)
    - Career Awareness Program For secondary school students, 1974 (Box-folder 9/5)
    - Center for Indian Teacher Education, 1978 (Box-folder 9/6)
    - Comparison of values: Indian and Non-Indian Graduate Students, 1970 (Box-folder 9/7)
    - Criteria for Analyzing Ethnic Bias in Instructional Material, 1975 (Box-folder 9/8)
    - Resource Unit on Animal Myths, undated (Box-folder 9/9)
    - Curriculum Components for focusing on Racism, Blacks, Latinos & Native Americans, 1975 (Box-folder 9/10)
    - Curricula Materials: Simulations Games (Box-folder 9/11)
    - Montana Reservation Presentation, Montana Native Americans, Reservations and Resources Overheads, 1994 (Box-folder 9/16)
    - "What Every Teacher Teaching should Know" Overheads, undated (Box-folder 9/17)
    - Educational Opportunity Center Fact Sheet, 1996 (Box-folder 9/20)
    - Freshman Interest Group Program, 1997 (Box-folder 9/21)
    - Bilingual-Bicultural, A goal in Indian Education is not new, 1974-1975 and undated (Box-folder 9/29)
    - Languages, Suggested reading lists, undated (Box-folder 10/5)
    - Make the world go away, Paper on Bicultural Education, 1976 (Box-folder 10/6)
    - Reading List: Contemporary Issues of the American Indian, undated (Box-folder 10/9)
    - Aspects of Indian Education by Constance McKay of the Courier Staff, undated (Box-folder 10/15)
    - American Indian History Course Outline, undated (same as Box 11, 30) (Box-folder 10/32)
    - Relationship of Teacher Education to Teaching, undated (Box-folder 11/27)
    - A Unit for Junior High Students on Native American Art, 1975 (Box-folder 11/29)
    - American Indian History Course Outline, undated (same as Box 10, 32) (Box-folder 11/30)
    - "Tribal Colleges: Shaping The Future of Native Americans", undated (Box-folder 11/35)
    - Montana State Department of Public Instruction, 1973 (Box-folder 12/21)
    - Address Delivered to 3rd Annual Indian High School Debate, 1973 (Box-folder 13/3)
    - Indian Education Confronts the Seventies, undated (Box-folder 13/5)
    - Developing a Native American Studies Program Teacher Corps Paper, 1973 (Box-folder 13/8)
    - The University and The Indian Student by Henrietta V. Whiteman, undated (Box-folder 13/12)
    - "Refocusing on Native American": A New Look at the Contemporary World of the Native American from a Political, Social and Educational Perspective, 1974 (Box-folder 14/5)
    - Values Education Exercise, Small Group Consensus, undated (Box-folder 15/4)
    - Steps For Outlining a Resource Unit, Pre-planning/teacher basic to Pupil-teacher Planning, undated (Box-folder 15/5)
    - Some examples of key concerns in the Establishment of goals & objectives Indian education, undated (Box-folder 15/6)
    - "So that All Indian Children will have equal educational Opportunity", 1975 (Box-folder 15/7)
    - Survey in Philosophical Aspects of Indian Education, undated (Box-folder 15/9)
    - Talent Delayed-Talent Denied, The Culturally Different Gifted Child, 1974 (Box-folder 15/10)
    - "Teaching About the American Indian", Civic Leader Article by William Crowder, Purdue University, 1968 (Box-folder 15/11)
    - Teaching Indian Children, 1974 and undated (Box-folder 15/12)
    - Teachers of Indian Children and Youth, undated (Box-folder 15/13)
    - Improve the Relevancy of Home Economics for Indian girls, 1971 (Box-folder 15/14)
    - Teaching Strategies/Newspaper Clippings, 1975-1977 and undated (Box-folder 15/15)
    - "Trouble Shooting: Problems Indian students meet" By Wayne Evans former director of Upward Bound, 1969 (Box-folder 15/19)
    - Vocational Education, 1976 (Box-folder 15/20)
    - The Testing of Native Americans BIA, Policy Recommendations, 1972 (Box-folder 15/21)
    - Title 4 Indian Education Act P L 92-318, Revision Of Impacted areas program as it relates to Indian Children, undated (Box-folder 15/22)
    - Teacher Corps, In-service Plan: to meet requirement of Indian Studies Law, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 15/23)
    - Teachers of Indian Children and Youth, undated (Box-folder 15/24)
    - Statistics Concerning Indian Education Fiscal year, 1976 (Box-folder 15/25)
    - Social Studies in BIA schools, Division of Education, A Position Paper by Max F. Harriger Social Science Specialist, 1968 (Box-folder 15/26)
    - Report to the Congress, National Advisory Council on Indian Education, 1974 (Box-folder 15/28)
    - Project View, Office of the Superintendent of Public Instruction, undated (Box-folder 16/9)
    - Quick Look At The U.S. Office of Education, undated (Box-folder 16/30)
    - Self-Determination Through Education, Workshop #1, undated (Box-folder 16/31)
    - Special Education is now a matter of Civil Rights, undated (Box-folder 16/34)
    - COSTEP Program, 1976 (Box-folder 17/5)
    - Educational Programs in the Health Field, 1974 (Box-folder 17/6)
    - Health Careers Curriculum, 1975 and undated (Box-folder 17/10)
    - UM Health Careers Curriculum, undated (Box-folder 17/11)
    - Financial Information For Native Americans In Health Careers, undated (Box-folder 17/12)
    - Health Careers Summer Program Harvard, 1978 (Box-folder 17/13)
    - IHS (Indian Health Services) Student Contact Forms, 1977 (Box-folder 17/14)
    - Medical School Admissions Requirements, Information For Minority Students, 1977 (Box-folder 17/18)
    - Medical School Hints, Preparing for University of Colorado Medical School, undated (Box-folder 17/19)
    - 5 Year Pre med program General Curriculum, 1977 and undated (Box-folder 18/4)
    - WICHE (Western Interstate Commission for Higher Education) Student Exchange Program, 1975-1977 (Box-folder 18/10)
    - Graduate and Professional Opportunities Program, 1978 (Box-folder 18/12)
    - Proceedings of Conference on G*POP (Graduate and Professional Opportunities Program) Proposals and the Role of Historically Black Colleges in Graduate Education, 1979 (Box-folder 18/14)
    - Health and Education Handbook, undated (Box-folder 19/7)
    - BIA Audit Report, Review of Higher Education Grant Program, 1976 (Box-folder 19/11)
    - Indian Careers In Health University of Montana, undated (Box-folder 19/14)
    - Indian Careers In Health, Objectives and NAS Programs, 1977 (Box-folder 19/15)
    - Indian Careers In Health Summer Institute, 1974-1978 (Box-folder 19/16)
    - Conference on American Indian culture and education, University of Montana, 1978 (Box-folder 19/17)
    - ICH (Indian Careers In Health) High School Student List, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 19/18)
    - 1976 Summer Institute, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 19/20)
    - 1977 Summer Institute (Box-folder 19/21)
    - 1978 Summer Institute, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 19/22)
    - Multicultural Education Research Project, Dawson: Indiana University, 1977 (Box-folder 19/23)
    - Final Evaluations of Summer Institute, 1977 (Box-folder 19/24)
    - G*POP Proposal, Application for Grants, 1982 (Box-folder 20/1)
    - G*POP Fellowships announcements, 1979 (Box-folder 20/2)
    - G*POP Program, 1979 (Box-folder 20/3)
    - G*POP Proposal, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 20/4)
    - G*POP Correspondence, 1976-1980 (Box-folder 20/5)
    - G*POP, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 20/6)
    - Graduate and Professional Fellowship Program, Proposal originals, 1978 (Box-folder 20/7)
    - G*POP Advisory Committee, Chair Person and Members, 1979 (Box-folder 20/8)
    - G*POP Final Report, Financial Status Report, 1979 (Box-folder 20/9)
    - G*POP Fellowship Programs, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 20/10)
    - G*POP Proposal, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 20/11)
    - G*POP Proposal, 1978 (Box-folder 20/12)
    - Graduate and Professional Fellowship Program, Proposal Coordination, 1979 (Box-folder 21/4)
    - Native Americans in Health Careers Ad Hoc Committee, 1973-1975 and undated (Box-folder 21/5)
    - Native Americans in Health Careers, 1975 (Box-folder 21/6)
    - Hansen Planetarium, Star Program of American Indian Sky Lore, 1976 (Box-folder 21/7)
    - Human Interaction, Team Leadership Cooperation and Coordinate Skills, undated (Box-folder 22/2)
    - Bibliography Supplement, Indian music, Culture, and Related Subjects, undated (Box-folder 22/3)
    - Bibliography Supplement, Drama, Fiction, Photographs, Poetry, Legends, undated (Box-folder 22/8)
    - Bibliography of Audio-Visual Aids, 1974-1980 (Box-folder 22/10)
    - Bibliography, Indians in literature, 1977 (Box-folder 22/11)
    - Bibliography, General, 1977 (Box-folder 22/12)
    - Bibliography of Native American Literature by Henri Whiteman and Clayton Small, undated (Box-folder 22/13)
    - Indian Programs at the University of Arizona, 1976 (Box-folder 23/13)
    - Pride in Heritage, Students Rap Education, 1971 (Box-folder 23/16)
    - Racism and Sexism, 10 quick ways to analyze children's books, 1976 (Box-folder 23/35)
    - Civil Rights Technical Assistance and Training Program, 1978 (Box-folder 23/41)
    - Student Rights, Strategy for prevention of genocide, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 24/1)
    - Thirteen Broad Concepts of Competencies, Teaching culturally diverse children, undated (Box-folder 24/28)
    - Oral & Written Traditions Handouts, 1984 and undated (Box-folder 24/29)
    - Multicultural Education and the American Indian, 1990-1991 and undated (Box-folder 24/30)
    - Communication between people with differing ethnic or racial backgrounds Workshop, undated (Box-folder 25/10)
    - Word Maze of Indian Tribes, undated (Box-folder 25/12)
    - Textbook Guidelines for cultural diversity, undated (Box-folder 25/13)
    - Board of Education Policy Statement on American Indian Education, 1984 (Box-folder 25/15)
    - Critical Incidents Exercise, undated (Box-folder 25/16)
    - Directory of Indian Education, 1987 (Box-folder 25/18)
    - Council on Interracial Books for Children Native Americans, undated (Box-folder 25/19)
    - From Boarding School to Self-Determination, 1987 (Box-folder 25/21)
    - Cultural Conflict and Traditional Curriculum, undated (Box-folder 25/22)
    - The Sacred Tree Teacher's Guide, 1984 (Box-folder 25/26)
  - Miscellaneous, Subseries 5
    - Art Exhibit, info sheet for award, undated (Box-folder 1/4)
    - Coleman Report, undated (Box-folder 1/6)
    - Comment, Vine Deloria, 1971 (Box-folder 1/7)
    - Form, Substance and Difference, 19th Annual Memorial Lecture, 1970 (Box-folder 1/9)
    - Foundations with involvement in Indian Affairs, undated (Box-folder 1/10)
    - Gene Leroy Hart Fair Trial Fund, 1977 and 1978 (Box-folder 1/11)
    - George Catlin's Creed about American Indians, undated (Box-folder 1/12)
    - Miscellaneous pictures, 1973-1990 and undated (Box-folder 1/18)
    - Atlanta Economic Review, Geothermal Energy, 1971 (Box-folder 2/23)
    - Dr. Lloyd C. Pickett, Some approaches to development and the Indian Dilemma, 1972 (Box-folder 2/24)
    - Dr. Helen Caldicott (effects of Nuclear Radiation) Fact Sheet, 1977 (Box-folder 3/1)
    - Environmental Quality Council, EQC Meeting, 1976 (Box-folder 3/2)
    - Ethno Botany Proposals, 1975 (Box-folder 3/4)
    - Department of Highways Tentative Construction Program, 1976-1981 (Box-folder 3/6)
    - Garrison Diversion Unit, A scientific and policy review, 1975 (Box-folder 3/8)
    - Hat Creek Project Statement of Environment Risk, 1978 (Box-folder 3/9)
    - High Lead logging costs1955 and, 1965 (Box-folder 3/10)
    - Indian People their land and their income in Billings, 1969 (Box-folder 3/11)
    - Livestock Range, It's nature and use bulletin, 1961 and 1971 (Box-folder 3/15)
    - Lower Flathead River Floaters guide, undated (Box-folder 3/16)
    - Missouri River Basin Commission Draft Minutes, 1977 and 1978 (Box-folder 3/17)
    - ESAA [Environmental Services Association of Alberta] Regulations, 1975 (Box-folder 4/22)
    - A Bibliography of funding source material, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 4/29)
    - Funding Equity A Legal Approach, 1970 (Box-folder 5/13)
    - Funding Offices Within OE, Programs with capability of funding education projects, undated (Box-folder 5/14)
    - Five Types of Young Indians, Which One Are You, 1964 (Box-folder 5/19)
    - Jerome Foundation, Inc., Grant application outline, 1971 (Box-folder 6/5)
    - Missoula's Speakers Directory, undated (Box-folder 6/40)
    - North American Indian Traditions and Religious Beliefs, undated (Box-folder 6/45)
    - From the Women's Bureau On Women, 1976-1981 (Box-folder 7/1)
    - American Indian Psychology Recruitment Program, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 7/4)
    - Native/Non-Native Ethics Day, 1997 (Box-folder 7/12)
    - Native American Day, 1997 (Box-folder 7/13)
    - Northwest Accreditation Information, 1998 (Box-folder 7/14)
    - Upward Bound Funding History, 1997 (Box-folder 7/17)
    - National Center for Education Statistics, 1995 (Box-folder 7/21)
    - 2426 Foreign Travel, 1997 (Box-folder 7/22)
    - School Official Tells View on Indian Studies, undated (Box-folder 7/23)
    - Suggested Indian Seminar and Speech Topics, undated (Box-folder 7/24)
    - Selected Publications, undated (Box-folder 7/25)
    - Selective Acculturation Without Assimilation (Box-folder 8/1)
    - Montana Indian Studies Law, 1995 (Box-folder 8/2)
    - Population Reference Bureau, Marriage, Divorce and living together: A teaching Module undated (Box-folder 8/17)
    - Preface, Critique written by Norman Lehrman, undated (Box-folder 8/18)
    - An Indian Community by Bob Ryan, undated (Box-folder 8/32)
    - The Indian Speaks, A response to the M.O.D. (Montanan's Opposing Discrimination), undated (Box-folder 8/35)
    - The Indian Today, Differentiating Traits, undated (Box-folder 8/37)
    - Articulation Agreements, 1996 (Box-folder 9/13)
    - Native Council Meetings, 1996-1997 and undated (Box-folder 9/14)
    - Catalog Course Change Forms, 1992 (Box-folder 9/15)
    - Bridges Program, 1997 (Box-folder 9/19)
    - Deloria, Vine, Colonies in Revolt, 1981 (Box-folder 9/22)
    - Being Indian Isà.By Rueben Snake, 1972 (Box-folder 9/23)
    - Big chief Sitting Bull goes on the Warpath, Pronounced Soo, not Si-ox, 1964 (Box-folder 9/24)
    - "Blazing A New Trail", Saturday Review, 1971 (Box-folder 9/25)
    - Bury My Heart at Wounded Knee By Dee Brown, undated (Box-folder 9/26)
    - Come Home, Mr. Chairman, poem dedicated to our industrious Chairman around country, undated (Box-folder 10/2)
    - Indian Names, undated (Box-folder 10/7)
    - Indian Land Areas Industrial Map, 1977 (Box-folder 10/8)
    - Indians Made their own Dyes By Jerry Laudermilk, 1968 (Box-folder 10/10)
    - How Horses First Came to Ha'a'ninin, undated (Box-folder 10/11)
    - Here's how the stick game is played, undated (Box-folder 10/12)
    - How to retain the Traditional Ways John Woodenlegs, undated (Box-folder 10/13)
    - Indian Dancing, 1921 (Box-folder 10/14)
    - Just Suppose, Indians Version of Redman in Contemporary Society, undated (Box-folder 10/18)
    - Indian Reserve Lands, Administering and question of legal status, undated (Box-folder 10/20)
    - Initials frequently used in Indian articles, undated (Box-folder 10/21)
    - Indians in Psychology Project, 1997 (Box-folder 10/22)
    - School of Pharmacy HCOP (Health Careers Opportunities Program), 1996-1997 (Box-folder 10/25)
    - Being Indian Isà.By Rueben Snake, 1970 (Box-folder 10/28)
    - American Indians, undated (Box-folder 10/30)
    - American Indians are unique in American Society, undated (Box-folder 10/31)
    - Ancestry Facts, Claims, undated (Box-folder 10/33)
    - Anxieties, The Anthropologist by Jorge Luis Borges, 1971 (Box-folder 10/34)
    - Are we giving America back to the Indians? Interstate Congress for equal rights and responsibilities, undated (Box-folder 10/35)
    - Arrival of the Whiteman by E. Bighorn Brockton, undated (Box-folder 10/36)
    - N.A. Clinical Psychology Program, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 10/38)
    - Missoula Indian Center, 1997 (Box-folder 10/39)
    - Native Americans and the United States, 1924, 1982 and undated (Box-folder 11/2)
    - Civil Rights and Biases of Native Americans, 1976 and undated (Box-folder 11/3)
    - Review of Indian Health Care, undated (Box-folder 11/4)
    - Native American Children lost, undated (Box-folder 11/5)
    - The Pain of Native Americans, 1977 and 1981 (Box-folder 11/6)
    - Native American Women, 1971-1980 and undated (Box-folder 11/7)
    - Look at Native Americans, 1972-1979 (Box-folder 11/8)
    - Irrigation and Native Americans, 1975-1978 (Box-folder 11/9)
    - Paviotso Child Training: Notes, undated (Box-folder 11/10)
    - Proposal for establishing an endowed honorary doctorate for John Woodenlegs Chair, 1977-1989 (Box-folder 11/11)
    - Demographics of Racial and Ethnic Distribution, 1996 (Box-folder 11/13)
    - Red Thunder Article, 1997 (Box-folder 11/17)
    - Saving Our Tongues Article, Indian Languages, 1996 (Box-folder 11/20)
    - Native Americans on Death Row, 1996 (Box-folder 11/21)
    - Student Minorities Award Article, 1996 (Box-folder 11/22)
    - UM Article on Native American Day, 1996 (Box-folder 11/23)
    - Indian Values compared to Non-Indian Values, undated (Box-folder 11/24)
    - Indian's Identification With The Earth, 1970 (Box-folder 11/25)
    - Basic Values, undated (Box-folder 11/26)
    - Museum of the Rockies, MSU, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 11/31)
    - Special Needs of American Indians with Handicaps, 1987-1989 (Box-folder 11/32)
    - About Henrietta Whiteman, 1978 (Box-folder 11/34)
    - Institute of Medicine & Humanities, 1996 (Box-folder 12/2)
    - U.W. West Foundation, Professor Rustem Medora, 1991 (Box-folder 12/3)
    - Retention and Remediation, 1964-1984 and undated (Box-folder 12/4)
    - Wells Report, 1989 (Box-folder 12/5)
    - Drug & Alcohol Advisory Committee, 1988-1989 and undated (Box-folder 12/6)
    - Articulation Agreement, 1991 (Box-folder 12/7)
    - Council Signals, 1988 (Box-folder 12/8)
    - Montana Constitution, Remarks by Marge Brown, 1990 (Box-folder 12/12)